A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Dept. of Alcoholic Beverage Control, 1934-1999
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Virginia Dept. of Alcoholic Beverage Control, 1934-1999
The Library of Virginia
53305
47 cu. ft. (47 boxes)
Virginia. Dept. of Alcoholic Beverage Control.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Virginia Alcoholic Beverage Control Authority, 17 May 2021.
Biographical Information
The Alcoholic Beverage Control Board and its administrative arm, the Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control, were created by an act of the General Assembly passed on March 7, 1934. The act, known as the Alcoholic Beverage Control Act, which the department was established to administer, specified the circumstances under which alcoholic beverages could be purchased and consumed. The act has been amended over the years. A major change occurred on February 7, 1968, when the General Assembly approved the sale of mixed drinks on a local option basis. The Board has three members appointed by the governor and confirmed by the General Assembly. It establishes rules and policies governing the Department, which controls through licenses and permits, the manufacture, bottling, selling, advertising, and transporting of alcoholic beverages; operates state stores for the sale of beverages, other than beer, to consumers and licensees. The Commissioner operates out of the Richmond office, with district offices established in Abingdon, Alexandria, Charlottesville, Chesapeake, Hampton, Lynchburg, Roanoke, and Staunton.
Scope and Content
Records, 1934-1999, including codes, legislation, orders, studies, and regulations of the Virginia Alcoholic Beverage Control Board. Topics include store hours, hearings, alcoholism, budgets, underage drinking, town meetings, and law enforcement, among others.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Regulatory Files, 1934-1995
Series II: Administrative Orders, 1940-1995
Series III: Legislation, 1952-1999
Series IV: Virginia Codes and Regulations, 1968-1998
Series V: Special Interest Items, 1971-1996
Contents List
- Series I: Regulatory Files, 1934-1995, Extent: 7 cu. ft. (7 boxes). (Box 1-7)
  - AD HOC Advisory Meeting Transcript, 1992 July 8 (Box 1)
  - Administrative "B" Orders, 1948 May - 1953 May (Box 1)
  - AD HOC Committee Members, 1987 (Box 1)
  - AD HOC Committee on Regs., 1988 April 21 (Box 1)
  - Request-AD HOC Panel & suggestion for changes in regulations, nd (Box 1)
  - Administrative Orders to, 1940 August 30 (Box 1)
  - AD Hoc Panel, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Orders Prior to, 1940 August 30 (Box 1)
  - Administrative "B" Orders, 1941 July-1945 March (Box 1)
  - Administrative "B" Orders, 1945 March-1946 December (Box 1)
  - Adopt New Section 67, 1975 May 1 (Box 1)
  - Abingdon Town Meeting, 1991 April 11 (Box 1)
  - Charlottesville Town Meeting, 1991 April 15 (Box 1)
  - Norfolk Town Meeting, 1991 March 28 (Box 1)
  - Northern Virginia Town Meeting, 1991 April 4 (Box 1)
  - Richmond Town Meeting, 1991 April 2 (Box 1)
  - Roanoke Town Meeting, 1991 April 11 (Box 1)
  - Spotysylvania Court House Town Meeting, 1991 April 8 (Box 1)
  - Board Orders 3780-14748, 1939 March 1-1955 April 11 (Box 1)
  - Board Orders 1256-3745, 1935 December 2-1937 February 18 (Box 1)
  - Board Orders 660-1255, 1934 December 5-1935 December 2 (Box 1)
  - Changes in Regulations, nd (Box 1)
  - Board Orders 26-548, 1934 April 13-November 8 (Box 1)
  - Board Orders 1-25, 1934 March 22-April 13 (Box 1)
  - Comments Public Hearing, 1987 November 19 (Box 1)
  - Div. of Legislative Automated Systems, nd (Box 1)
  - Governor's Mgmt. Study Report, nd (Box 1)
  - Regulations, 1980 May 27 (Box 1)
  - Regulations, 1979 May 24 (Box 1)
  - Regulations, 1985 October 22 (Box 1)
  - Regulations, 1981 May 12 (Box 1)
  - Regulations, 1986 September 23 (Box 2)
  - Regulations, 1989 September 20 (Box 2)
  - Regulations, 1987 November 19 (Box 2)
  - Regulations, Excerpt Sec. 27-57.1, 1981 (Box 2)
  - Regulation Hearing, 1983 December 15 (Box 2)
  - Regulations Hearings, 1982 June 16-July 1 (Box 2)
  - Regulation Hearing, 1984 September 18 (Box 2)
  - Regulations, 1976 May 10 (Box 2)
  - Regulations Hearings, 1972 January 31 (Box 2)
  - Regulations, 1975 May 29 (Box 2)
  - Regulations, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Emergency Regulation (Did Not Go Forth), nd (Box 2)
  - Hearing on Regulations, 1971 December 16 (Box 2)
  - Happy Hour, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Happy Hour, 1985 January-February (Box 2)
  - Happy Hour Public Hearing, 1985 March 7 (Box 2)
  - Happy Hour, 1985 March-May (Box 2)
  - Happy Hour, 1985 August-November (Box 2)
  - Written Comments Happy Hour, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Happy Hour Public Hearing, 1985 April 7 (Box 3)
  - Section 16 of VR125-01-5 Happy Hour, nd (Box 3)
  - Hearing on Regulation Section 19.1, nd (Box 3)
  - Hearings, 1987 November 19 (Box 3)
  - Hearing Day, Transcript Regulations, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Post Hearing Regulations, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Keg Regulation Letters, nd (Box 3)
  - Licenses - Extension of, nd (Box 3)
  - Master Copy of Board Regs. for ABC Act, Effective, 1960 December 1 (Box 3)
  - Opposition Letters Regulations, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Pre-Hearing Regs., 1987 (Box 3)
  - Orders Covering Special Markups, 1935 July-1938 January (Box 3)
  - Regulations, Pre-hearing, 1984 September (Box 3)
  - Regulations, Pre-hearing, 1988 September (Box 3)
  - Regulation Hearing, 1990 January 15 (Box 4)
  - Proposed Regulations, 1988 (Box 4)
  - Proposed Regulation, Opposition Letters, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Regulations, Public Hearing, 1987 November 19 (Box 4)
  - Public Hearing, 1988 September 20 (Box 4)
  - Transcript Public Hearing, 1991 June 20 (Box 4)
  - Public Hearing - VR125-01-1 Section 1.16-O/C, nd (Box 4)
  - Public Hearing, Comments From Public Re: Regs., 1986 September 23 (Box 4)
  - Public Meeting, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Public Meeting, 1988 June 2 (Box 4)
  - Rationing Regulations, nd (Box 4)
  - Regulations, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Regulations Regulatory Notices, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Regulations, nd (Box 5)
  - Regulations, Registrar Post Hearing A-256 (File No. 2), 1993 (Box 5)
  - Regulations, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Regulations Data, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Regulations Constituent Correspondence, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Regulations Emergency Regulations, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Regulations House Document No. 51, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Regulations, Letters to the Agency, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Regulations, New Sections Old Sections-Booklet, nd (Box 5)
  - Regulations, Ad hoc & Public Meeting, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Reg. Meeting, 1985 October 22 (Box 5)
  - Regulation Hearing Section 55, nd (Box 5)
  - Regulations, Post Hearing A-256, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Regulations Prior to, 1940 August 30 (Box 5)
  - Regulations Prior to, 1940 August 30 (Box 6)
  - Regulation Suggestions, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Orders Prior to, 1940 August 30 (Box 6)
  - Regs. Read into the Records, 1988 (Box 6)
  - Regulations Proposed Changes-In House, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Regulations Proposed Changes Outside ABC, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Regulations Recodification Rollins Working Papers, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Regulations Secretary Rollins, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Regulations (Working Papers), 1987 (Box 6)
  - Regulations, 1988 (Box 6)
  - State Legislative Study Commission, nd (Box 6)
  - Statute & Regulations Affecting Regs., 1970 forward (Box 6)
  - Public Meeting, 1988 June 2 (Box 6)
  - Statute & Regulations Affecting Regs., 1978-1988 (Box 7)
  - Study Commission, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
  - ABC Study Commission, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Suggestions for Changes in Regs. Public Meeting, 1988 June 2 (Box 7)
  - Suggestions for Regulation Changes, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Town Meeting, 1995 (Box 7)
- Series II: Administrative Orders, 1940-1995, Extent: 11 cu. ft. (11 boxes). (Box 8-18)
  - B-1 - Administrative Orders, 1940 (Box 8)
  - A-1; also B-1, 1940 (Box 8)
  - A-1-E, 1941 June 29 (Box 8)
  - A-2-HOURS OF SALE MIDDLESEX CO., 1940 October (Box 8)
  - A-3-CHRISTIANBURG HOURS OF SALE, 1940 October (Box 8)
  - A-5-DAYLIGHT SAVINGS TIME PREVAILING, 1941 (Box 8)
  - A-6-D.S.T IN A-5 NOT APPLICABLE TO ALEXANDRIA & CITIES OF ARLINTON & FAIRFAX, 1941 August (Box 8)
  - A-7-SECTION 36 OF A-1 AMENDED & READOPTED FORMS, 1942 June (Box 8)
  - A-8 SECTIONS 4, 5, 6, & 7 -WART TIME APPLICATION, 1942 October (Box 8)
  - A-9 SECTIONS OF A-1 AMENDED & READOPTED 31, 50 (C), 53, 55, 56, 59, 63 & 66, 1942 December-1943 January (Box 8)
  - A-10 RATIONING REGULATION, 1943 January (Box 8)
  - A-11 RATIONING REGULATION, 1943 January (Box 8)
  - A-12 RATIONING REGULATION, 1943 February (Box 8)
  - A-13 RATIONING REGULATION, 1943 March (Box 8)
  - A-14 RATIONING REGULATION, 1943 April-May (Box 8)
  - A-15 EXTENSION OF LICENSES FOR 1942-43, 1943 June-July (Box 8)
  - A-16 RATIONING REGULATION, 1943 July-August (Box 8)
  - A-17 RATIONING REGULATION, 1943 September (Box 8)
  - A-19 RATIONING REGULATION, 1944 February-March (Box 8)
  - A-20 RATIONING REGULATION, 1944 March-April (Box 8)
  - A-21 WHAT TIME SHALL BE APPLICABLE, 1946 April (Box 8)
  - A-22 RATIONING REGULATION, 1946 May-June (Box 8)
  - A-23 SACRAMENTAL, METHOD OF ACQUIRING, ETC., 1946 June (Box 8)
  - A-24 PERMITS FOR RELEASE OF A. BS. IN US REV. WHSES TO SHIPS, 1946 June (Box 8)
  - A-25 SECTION 89-ADV. OF A. BS. TO CONFORM TO REGS. OF BD., 1946 November (Box 8)
  - "A-26 PERMITS FOR RELEASE OF A.BS. IN US REVENUE WHSES. TO SHIPS A-24 RESCINDED, 1946 November-December (Box 8)
  - A-27 RATIONING REGULATION, 1946 December-1947 January (Box 8)
  - A-28 RATIONING REGULATION, 1946 December-1947 January (Box 8)
  - A-29 RATIONING REGULATION, 1947 May-June (Box 8)
  - A-30 RATIONING REGULATION, 1947 June-July (Box 8)
  - A-31 SECTION 52 OF SALES OF WINE OUTSIDE OF VA. AMENDED & READOPTED, 1947 December (Box 8)
  - "A-32 CULINARY PERMITS 7/9/48 - 7/15/48 REPLACED BY A-33, 1948 November (Box 8)
  - A-33 CULINARY PERMITS A-32 AMENDED & READOPTED, 1948 November (Box 8)
  - A-34 SECTIONS 4, 5, 6 & 7 AMENDED & READOPTED - WAR TIME TO EASTERN STANDARD TIME, 1950 April (Box 8)
  - A-35 SECTION 8.1 OF A-1 AMENDED & READOPTED DISTILLED SPIRITS ADV., 1950 April-June (Box 8)
  - A-36 SECTION 5.1 VIRGINIA HOURS OF SALE, 1950 July (Box 8)
  - A-37 SECTION 5.2 NORFOLK HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1950 July (Box 8)
  - A-38 SECTION 5.3 VA. BEACH HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1950 July (Box 8)
  - A-39 SECTION 5.4 PORTSMOUTH HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1950 July (Box 8)
  - A-40 SECTION 5.5 NEWPORT NEWS HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1950 August (Box 8)
  - A-41 SECTION 5.6 ELIZABETH CITY HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1950 September (Box 8)
  - A-42 SECTION 5.7 WARWICK CO. HOURS OF OPERATION, 1950 September (Box 8)
  - A-43 SECTION 5.8 PHOEBUS HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1950 September (Box 8)
  - A-44 SECTION 5.9 SOUTH NORFOLK HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1950 September (Box 8)
  - A-45 SECTION 5.10 CAMPBELL CO. HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1950 December-1951 January (Box 8)
  - A-46 SECTION 5.11 CHINCOTEAGUE HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1950 December-1951 January (Box 8)
  - A-47 SECTION 5.12 CREWE HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1951 February (Box 8)
  - A-48 SECTION 5.13 ACCOMACK CO. HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1951 February (Box 8)
  - A-49 SECTION 5.14 PARKSLEY HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1951 March (Box 8)
  - A-50 SECTION 5.15 CAMPBELL CO. HOURS OF SALE RESCINDED (A-45 - 12/28/50), 1951 April (Box 8)
  - A-51 SECTION 5.16 ONACOCK HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1951 May (Box 8)
  - A-52 SECTION 5.17 PAINTER HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1951 May (Box 8)
  - A-53 SECTION 5.18 PRINCE EDWARD CO. HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1951 May (Box 8)
  - A-54 SECTION 5.19 COLONIAL HGTS. HOURS OF SALE, 1951 May (Box 8)
  - A-55 SECTION 5.20 COLONIAL HGTS. HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1951 June-July (Box 8)
  - A-56 SECTION 5.21 PETERSBURG HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1951 June-July (Box 8)
  - A-57 SECTION 5.22 HOPEWELL HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1951 June-July (Box 8)
  - A-58 SECTION 78-ADV. OF A. BS. SIGNS, ETC. ADOPTED, 1951 December-1952 January (Box 8)
  - A-59 SECTIONS 85, 86 & 87 REPEALED (8/30/40) - SECTIONS 85, 86 ADOPTED ADV. SIGNS, 1951 December-1952 January (Box 8)
  - A-60 SECTIONS 5.23 STAFFORD CO. HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1952 January-February (Box 8)
  - A-61 SECTION 5.24 DINWIDDIE CO. HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1952 April (Box 8)
  - A-62 SECTION 5.25 ALEXANDRIA HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1952 April (Box 8)
  - A-63 SECTION 5.26 TOWN OF COLONIAL BEACH HOURS OF SALE, 1952 May (Box 8)
  - A-64 SECTION 8.1 - ADOPTED DAYLIGHT SAVINGS TIME NORFOLK CITY & CO., VA. BEACH, PRINCESS ANNE CO., 1952 June (Box 8)
  - A-69 SECTIONS 100, 101, 102, 103 104 & 105 ADOPTED, 1952 June (Box 8)
  - A-70 thru A-75, 1952-1953 (Box 8)
  - A-73 SECTIONS 5.29 & 5.30 ADOPTED SECS. 78, 89.1, 98, AMENDED & READOPTED & SECTION 78, 1953 April-June (Box 8)
  - A-76 thru A-79, 1953-1960 (Box 8)
  - A-85 SECTION 5.49 COUNTY OF HENRICO HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED, 1960 June-July (Box 8)
  - A-87 SECTION 47.6 AMENDED & READOPTED, 1960 June-July (Box 8)
  - A-88 SECTION 63.2 ADOPTED, BONDS TO BE FILED BY WHOLESALERS, ETC., 1960 June-July (Box 8)
  - A-89 SECTION 63.1 AMENDED & READOPTED, BOND FILED BY WHOLESALERS, ETC., 1960 July (Box 8)
  - "A-94 SECTIONS 80, 24, 19 & 20 ADOPTED SECTION 85 AMENDED & READOPTED, 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - A-65 thru A-68, 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - A-80 thru A-87, 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - A-90 thru A-96, 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - A97 thru A-99, 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - A-101 SECTION 5.43 BUENA VISTA ADOPTED HOURS OF SALE, 1961 October-November (Box 8)
  - A-102 SECTION 5.44 ROANOKE CITY ADOPTED HOURS OF SALE, 1962 January (Box 8)
  - A-103 SECTION 5.45 ROANOKE CO. ADOPTED HOURS OF SALE, 1962 April (Box 8)
  - A-104 SECTION 5.46 BOTETOURT CO. ADOPTED HOURS OF SALE, 1962 May-June (Box 8)
  - A-105 SECTIONS 5.47, 5.48, 5.49 & 5.50 ADOPTED HOURS OF SALE, 1962 (Box 8)
  - A-106 SECTIONS 5.51, 5.53 HOURS OF SALE BIG STONE GAP, MONTROSS, & LEE COUNTY, 1962 (Box 8)
  - A-107 SECTION 4 - SALE & CONSP. IN LOCALITIES - SUNDAY BAN REPEALED, 1962 July (Box 9)
  - A-108 SECTION 47 WHSES FOR STORAGE OF A BS, NOT UNDER BOND - ADOPTED SECTION 41-STERNO, 1962 July-September (Box 9)
  - A-109 SECTION 5.54 ALBEMARLE CO. ADOPTED HOURS OF SALE, 1962 August-September (Box 9)
  - A-110 SECTION 5.55 HOURS OF SALE ADOPTED SECTION 80 ADVERTISING AMENDED & READOPTED, 1962 (Box 9)
  - A-111 SECTION 56 WINCHESTER ADOPTED HOURS OF SALE, 1962 December (Box 9)
  - A-112 SECTION 5.57 TOWN OF POUND ADOPTED HOURS OF SALE, 1963 May (Box 9)
  - A-113 SECTION 5.58 DAMASCUS ADOPTED HOURS OF SALE, 1953 May (Box 9)
  - A-114 SECTION 5.59 BUCHANAN CO. ADOPTED HOURS OF SALE, 1963 July (Box 9)
  - A-115 SECTIONS 5.60 & 5.61 HOURS OF SALE, 1963 July (Box 9)
  - A-116 SECTION 5.9 - REPEALED 9/30/63 SECTIONS 5.9 & 4.62 ADOPTED 9/30/67 HOURS OF SALE, 1963 September (Box 9)
  - A-118 ADOPTED SECTIONS - 5.1, 5.3, 5.6, 5.7, 5.8, 5.28 & 8.2 REPEALED SECTIONS 5.3, 5.8, 5.28 & 5.63 HOURS OF SALE, 1963 (Box 9)
  - A-119 SECTION 5.64 TOWN OF LEESBURG ADOPTED HOURS OF SALE, 1964 December (Box 9)
  - A-120 SECTIONS 9 & 20 AMENDED & READOPTED, 1965 February-March (Box 9)
  - A-121 SECTION 9 AMENDED & READOPTED, 1965 March-April (Box 9)
  - A-123 SECTION 5.65 STAUNTON ADOPTED HOURS OF SALE, 1965 July (Box 9)
  - A-126 SECTION 85 ADVERTISING TRUCKS AMENDED & READOPTED, 1965 December-1966 January (Box 9)
  - A-127 SECTION 5.68 HILLSVILLE ADOPTED HOURS OF SALE, 1966 June-July (Box 9)
  - A-128 SECTIONS 9, 14, 17, 21, 64 & 65 AMENDED SECTION 66 REPEALED, 1966 July-August (Box 9)
  - A-129 SECTION 5.69 GREENE CO. ADOPTED HOURS OF SALE, 1966 August-September (Box 9)
  - A-131 SECTION 89.1 SIGNS BEERS OFFERED FOR SALE AMENDED & READOPTED, 1967 March-April (Box 9)
  - A-132 SECTIONS 5.3 & 5.4 HOURS OF SALE, 1967 April (Box 9)
  - A-133 SECTION 5.2 CITY OF NORFOLK HOURS OF SALE AMENDED & READOPTED, 1967 April (Box 9)
  - A-134 SECTIONS 5.71 & 5.62 HOURS OF SALE, 1967 (Box 9)
  - A-135 SECTION 5.8 CITY OF HAMPTON AMENDED & READOPTED HOURS OF SALE, 1968 April (Box 9)
  - A-136 thru A-140, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - A-139 SECTION 5.74 HAYSI TOWN HOURS OF SALE, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - A-140 SECTIONS 5.11 - CHINCOTEAGUE; 5.77 - DICKERSON CO.; 5.78 - LOUISA HOURS OF SALE, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - A-122 thru A-142, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - A-143 SECTION 5.10 CAMPBELL CO., SECTION 5.82 CHARLES CITY CO. HOURS OF SALE, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - A-145 SECTIONS 5.21 PETERSBURG HOURS OF SALE AMENDED & READOPTED, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - A-144 thru A-148, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - A-154 SECTION 5.85 RESTRICTED HOURS COUNTY OF SOUTHHAMPTON, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - A-156, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - A-157 SECTIONS 6, 7, 24, 53, 54, 55, 78, 8.1, 27.1, 34.1, 46.1, 46.2, 46.4, 52.1, 52.2, 60 & 70.1, 1968 September (Box 9)
  - A-159, 1968 (Box 9)
  - A-169 SECTIONS 37 & 37-1, 1968 (Box 9)
  - A-161 RESCINDING 1-160 RESTRICTED HOURS NEWPORT NEWS, VA. EFFECTIVE, 1968 September (Box 9)
  - A-162 SECTION 5-89 ISLE OF WRIGHT COUNTY HOURS OF SALE, 1968 (Box 9)
  - A-163 SECTIONS 34, 46-3 & 58, 1968 (Box 9)
  - A-152 thru A-164, 1968 (Box 9)
  - A-165 HOURS OF SALE BATH COUNTY SECTION 5-90, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - A-166 SECTIONS 37 ADOPTED, 1969 January (Box 9)
  - A-170 RESTRICTED HOURS SECTION 5.70 MCKENNY AMENDED SECTION 5.93 WILLIAMSBURG ADOPTED, 1969 (Box 9)
  - A-171 SECTION 5-94 RESTRICTED HOURS COUNTY OF LOUNDOUN, 1969 June (Box 10)
  - A-173 RESTRICTED HOURS SECTIONS 5-53 & 5-97 COUNTIES - LEE & MONTGOMERY RESPECTIVELY, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - A-172 thru A-176, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - A-176 thru A-180, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - A-177 thru A-181, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - A-182 RESCINDING SECTIONS 5-4, 5-48 RESTRICTED HOURS PORTSMOUTH, ALEXANDRIA, CHARLOTTESVILLE, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - A-183 SECTIONS 5.39 & 5.90 RESCINDED HOURS OF SALE, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - A-184 SECTIONS 53 & 70 AMENDED & READOPTED, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - A-185 SECTIONS 5-36, 5-45 & 5-91 RESCINDED HOURS OF SALE, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - A-186 SECTION 5-9 RESCINDED HOURS OF SALE, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - A-187 SECTION 5-54 RESCINDED HOURS OF SALE ALBERMARLE COUNTY, 1970 April (Box 10)
  - A-188 SECTION 40 PURCHASE OF A.BS. OR BS. BY ONE PERSON FOR ANOTHER, 1970 April (Box 10)
  - A-189 SECTION 5-21 RESCINDED HOURS OF SALE CITY OF PETERSBURG, 1970 May (Box 10)
  - A-190 SECTION 5-64 RESCINDED TOWN OF LEESBURG, 1970 May (Box 10)
  - A- 191 SECTION 5-41 AMENDED & READOPTED COUNTY OF ALLEGHANY, 1970 May (Box 10)
  - A-192 SECTION 42 AMENDED & READOPTED, 1970 June-July (Box 10)
  - A-193 SECTION 14 AMENDED & READOPTED, 1970 June-July (Box 10)
  - A-194 SECTION 19 RESCINDED, 1970 June-July (Box 10)
  - A-195 SECTION 14.1 ADOPTED 15-AMENDED & READOPTED, 1970 June (Box 10)
  - A-196 SECTION 40.1 RESCINDED, 1970 June (Box 10)
  - A-197 SECTION 13 AMENDED & READOPTED, 1970 July (Box 10)
  - A-198 SECTION 9 AMENDED & READOPTED, 1970 August (Box 10)
  - A-199 SECTION 25, 1970 August-September (Box 10)
  - A-200 SECTION 24 DESIGNATED MANGERS, 1970 October-November (Box 10)
  - A- 201 SECTION 5.62 RESCINDED HOURS OF SALE CITY OF YORK EFFECTIVE, 1971 January (Box 10)
  - A-202 SECTIONS 59.5, 71 & 80, 1971 April (Box 10)
  - A-203 SECTION 5.56 HOURS OF SALE CITY OF WINCHESTER RESCINDED, 1971 May (Box 10)
  - A-204 SECTION 74 AMENDED & READOPTED ADVERTISING PROGRAMS, 1971 August (Box 10)
  - A-205 SECTION 12 AMENDED & READOPTED, 1971 December-1972 January (Box 10)
  - A-206 SECTION 5 AMENDED & READOPTED, 1971 December (Box 10)
  - A-207 RESCINDING CERTAIN SECTIONS 2-64 ADOPTING OTHER SECTIONS, 1972 May (Box 10)
  - A-208 AMENDING, READOPTING & RENUMBERING CERTAIN SECTIONS, 1972 June-July (Box 10)
  - A-209 ADOPTING SECTION 53 CLUB APPLICATIONS, 1972 June-July (Box 10)
  - A-210 ADOPTING SECTION 54 PRICE POSTING, 1972 June-September (Box 10)
  - A-211 SECTION 5 AMENDED VIRGINIA BEACH, 1972 July-August (Box 10)
  - A-212 SECTION 5 AMENDED CITY OF SALEM EFFECTIVE, 1972 August (Box 10)
  - A-213 SECTION 5 AMENDED CITY OF NORFOLK, CITY OF FREDERICKSBURG & SPOTSYLVANIA, 1972 September (Box 10)
  - A-214 SECTIONS 14 & 15 AMENDED & READOPTED, 1972 (Box 10)
  - A-215 SECTIONS 13, 32 - 39 WINE CONTAINERS; DEPOSITS; MIXED B.1. AMENDED & READOPTED, 1972 (Box 10)
  - A-216 SECTION 55 LEW OR DISORDERLY CONDUCT, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - A-217 SECTION 5 HOURS OF SALE; CITY OF SALEM - AMENDED & READOPTED UNTIL 1:00 AM YEAR ROUND, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - A-218 SECTION 5 AMENDED & READOPTED - VA. BEACH, NORFOLK, CHESAPEAKE & PORTSMOUTH AMENDED & READOPTED; ADVERTISING, INDOORS, SPECIALTIES, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - A-219 SECTION 54-1, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - A-219 SECTION 54-2, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - A-219 SECTION 54-3, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - A-219 AMENDED, 1973 August-September (Box 11)
  - A-219 AMENDED & READOPTED SECTION 54 PRICE POSTING, 1973 September (Box 11)
  - A-220 SECTIONS 14 & 15 AMENDED & READOPTED HANDLING & MARKUP OF WINE EFFECTIVE, 1973 October (Box 11)
  - A-221 AMENDED & READOPTED SECTION 5 HOURS OF SALE EFFECTIVE, 1974 May (Box 11)
  - A-222 AMENDED & READOPTED SECTIONS 1, 3, 4,39, 41, 50 & 51 EFFECTIVE, 1974 July (Box 11)
  - A-223 SECTION 5.1 CITY OF DANVILLE EFFECTIVE, 1974 May (Box 11)
  - A-224 AMENDED & READOPTED SECTIONS 12, 13, 31, 34 & 51.1. EFFECTIVE, 1974 July (Box 11)
  - A-225 READOPTION OF SECTION 5.1 HOURS OF SALES DANVILLE EFFECTIVE, 1974 July (Box 11)
  - A-226 AMENDED & READOPTED SECTION 51.1 FORTIFIED WINE EFFECTIVE, 1974 August (Box 11)
  - A-227 DANVILLE HOURS EFFECTIVE, 1974 August (Box 11)
  - A-229 AMENDING SECTIONS 4, 5, 14, 41, 51 & 61, 1975 August (Box 11)
  - A-230 REGS. 4, 5, 10, 13, 14, 39, 41, 61 HEARING, 1976 May (Box 11)
  - A-231 SECTION 34 REGS. HEARING, 1976-1977 (Box 11)
  - A-232, 1977 May (Box 11)
  - A-233 12, 16, 31, 43, 51, 54.1, 61, 63, 66, 1977 December (Box 11)
  - A-234 (4), 1978-1979 (Box 12)
  - A234 (1) 1978 REG. CHANGES, 1978 (Box 12)
  - A-234 (2), 1978 (Box 12)
  - A-234 (3), 1978 (Box 12)
  - A-235 NOTICE OF HEARINGS MAY 1979 REGISTER OFFICE, ETC., 1979 (Box 12)
  - A-235 HEARINGS BEFORE COMM., 1979 May (Box 12)
  - A-235 WRITTEN COMMENTS RE: PROPOSALS, 1979 (Box 12)
  - A-235 WRITTEN COMMENTS RE: PROPOSALS (OPEN DOOR NOTICES), 1979 (Box 12)
  - A-235 WRITTEN COMMENTS RE: PROPOSALS, 1979 (Box 12)
  - A-235 HEARINGS BEFORE COMM., 1979 May (Box 12)
  - A-235 WRITTEN COMMENTS RE: PROPOSALS, 1979 (Box 12)
  - A-235 WRITTEN COMMENTS RE: PROPOSALS, 1979 (Box 12)
  - A-235 WRITTEN COMMENTS RE: PROPOSALS, 1979 (Box 12)
  - A-236 RULES OF PRACTICE, 1979 (Box 13)
  - A-237 SECTION 5.2 VA. BEACH EMERGENCY, 1979 (Box 13)
  - A-238, 1979 (Box 13)
  - A-239 PREHEARING, 1979-1981 (Box 13)
  - A-239 HEARING, 1979-1981 (Box 13)
  - A-240 (copy) REGS., 1981 May (Box 13)
  - A-240 DRAFTS - REGS. 1981 APPROVED 50-69, 1981 (Box 13)
  - A-240 ORIGINAL REGULATIONS, 1981 May (Box 13)
  - A-240 REGS 1981 1-49, 1981 (Box 13)
  - A-240, 1981 (Box 13)
  - A-240 REGS., 1981 (Box 13)
  - A-240 PUBLIC NOTICE, 1981 (Box 13)
  - A-240 REGS. GENERAL, 1981 (Box 13)
  - A-241, 1982 (Box 13)
  - A-241 REGS. PREHEARING, 1982 (Box 13)
  - A-241 HEARING, 1982 June (Box 14)
  - A-242 TRANSCRIPT, 1983 December (Box 14)
  - A-242 HEARING GOV'S APPROVAL, 1983 December (Box 14)
  - A-242 REGS. PRE & POST HEARING, 1983 December (Box 14)
  - A-243 TRANSCRIPT COPY, 1984 (Box 14)
  - A-243 REGS. POST HEARING, 1984 September (Box 14)
  - A-243 DAY OF HEARING, 1984 (Box 14)
  - A-234 TRANSCRIPT ORIGINAL, 1984 (Box 14)
  - A-244 EMERGENCY REG., 1984-1985 (Box 14)
  - A-245 EMERGENCY REG., 1984-1985 (Box 14)
  - A-246 PREHEARING, 1985 October (Box 14)
  - A-246 POST HEARING, 1985 October (Box 14)
  - A-246 HEARING DAY, 1985 October (Box 14)
  - A-246 HEARINGS ON REGS., 1985 October (Box 14)
  - A-247 CATERER'S LICENSE, 1985 (Box 14)
  - A-248 POST HEARING, 1985-1986 (Box 15)
  - A-248 HEARING DAY, 1986 September (Box 15)
  - A-248 PREHEARING, 1986 (Box 15)
  - A-249 WORKING COPIES, 1987 (Box 15)
  - A-249 POST HEARING WORKING PAPERS, 1987 (Box 15)
  - A-250 POST HEARING, 1988 (Box 15)
  - A-251 SECTION 13 OF VR125-01-7, 1989 (Box 15)